// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!


// Title: I Need Some Space
module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'When was the first written record of the card game Solitaire?', 
      a: '500 BC', 
      b: '1022 CE',
      c: '1783 CE',
      d: 'March 2020',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of these is NOT a slang term for solitary confiment in prisons worldwide?', 
      a: 'The Shoe', 
      b: 'The Cooler',
      c: 'AdSeg',
      d: 'The Wee Tin',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What key brain functions have scientists observed to decrease as a result of chronic social isolation?', 
      a: 'senses of smell and taste', 
      b: 'learning and memory',
      c: 'autonomic regulation',
      d: 'movement and balance',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What country has the lowest population density in the world?', 
      a: 'Russia', 
      b: 'Mongolia',
      c: 'Canada',
      d: 'Australia',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the largest recorded gathering of humans in history?', 
      a: 'Ayatollah Khomeini\'s Funeral', 
      b: 'Cubs World Series parade',
      c: 'Hindu Kumbh Mela Pilgrimmage',
      d: 'Muslim Arba\'een Pilgrimage',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where is the most remote airport in the world from another airport?', 
      a: 'Easter Island', 
      b: 'Hawaii',
      c: 'New Zealand',
      d: 'The South Pole',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which country\'s citizens need the least \'personal space\' from strangers, according to a 2016 study?', 
      a: 'Estonia', 
      b: 'Hong Kong',
      c: 'United States',
      d: 'Argentina',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the most densely populated city in the world?', 
      a: 'Manila', 
      b: 'Mumbai',
      c: 'Port-au-Prince',
      d: 'Guttenberg, New Jersey',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What artist first recorded the power ballad "All By Myself"?', 
      a: 'Celine Dion', 
      b: 'Eric Carmen',
      c: 'Barbara Streisand',
      d: 'Todd Rundgren',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the card game Solitaire called in Europe?', 
      a: 'Cards-for-One', 
      b: 'Singular',
      c: 'Boring',
      d: 'Patience',
      answer: 'd'
    }
  ]
};